directorpoint.com 2014-03-14

# Privacy Policy | Directorpoint

**Privacy Policy**

We understand and respect the importance of personal identity and information. 

Directorpoint LLC ("Directorpoint") Privacy Policy Last Updated: January 14, 2013 

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.directorpoint.com and our mobile application. The statement does not apply to our practices on other websites or offline. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us. 

This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website www.directorpoint.com and our mobile application. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Directorpoint. 

**Security**

The security of your personal information and our clients' information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as your password), or when data is transmitted through our app we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us. 

**What We Collect**

You may browse our site without providing us any information that is identifiable for you. When using our app we will collect the OS version you are using in order to ensure that the application is presented to you properly. We do not ask you for, access or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our app or services. 

We use your IP address and other log file information to help administer our servers and website.  We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

If Directorpoint is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

Directorpoint collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. Directorpoint works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected. Directorpoint may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients. Directorpoint has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Client (the board administrator). If the Client requests Directorpoint to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days. Directorpoint will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Directorpoint will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Directorpoint is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any sites that www.directorpoint.com may provide links to. 

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by making the change on our member account pages, or by contacting us. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. 

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you have any questions about this privacy and security statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us via email or mail us at Directorpoint LLC, 2100B SouthBridge Parkway, Suite 240, Birmingham, AL 35209.
